(Sheldon:)Did you enjoy
my lecture?
(Amy:)No, and neither did
our waiter.
(Sheldon:)Well, if you're going to
serve Cornish game hen,
(Sheldon:)you should either be familiar
with the history of Cornwall
(Sheldon:)or be prepared
to learn it.
(Amy:)It's hard to argue with that.
(Amy:)And I know because I saw a
sad man with a pepper mill
(Amy:)desperately try and fail.
(Penny:)Hey, how was dinner?
(Sheldon:)Good, I had Cornish game hen.
(Leonard:)Oh, that poor waiter.
(Amy:)Sheldon, how about tomorrow
night we see a movie?
(Penny:)You guys are going out
two nights in a row?
(Sheldon:)I missed a number of date nights
while I was on my train trip,
(Sheldon:)and I'm contractually
obligated to make them up
(Sheldon:)under the terms of the
Relationship Agreement.
(Penny:)That's so hot.
(Amy:)It's better than hot,
it's binding.
(Sheldon:)If you're free
tomorrow night,